you will be prosecutors Yes
вы будете прокурорами Да
cool Hello
прикольно
Hello I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk And you are from Russia
Хмельницке А вы из России
where Rostov-on-Don is from I know I know such a
откуда ростов-на Дону о знаю знаю такой
big city There is a million million people like a
горо большой Там миллион миллионник типа
city yes And I know Syktyvkar you know
города да А я Сыктывкара знаете знаю
Komi Komi SSR Well it was by now
Коми Коми ССР Ну было ко сейчас
Komi Republic Yes yes yes A  I’m from
Республика Коми Да да да А я из
Khmelnitsky, you know where it is No,
Хмельницкого знаете где это Нет к
unfortunately due
сожалению дуе
Ermolin
ермолин
pony here Dunaevtsy Yarmolintsy here
пони вот Дунаевцы ярмолинцы тут
Khmelnitsky here letichev here
Хмельницкий тут летичев тут
Volochysk Okay BC I
Волочиск Ладно ВС
know And you are 18 years old, at least of course you’re
знаю А вам по 18 лет есть хоть конечно
studying to be a prosecutor
на кого учитесь на прокурору
about you will be prosecutors Yes
проро вы будете прокурорами Да
Cool And it’s interesting for you to become a prosecutor,
Прикольно А вы зате прокурора пойти
well  I’ve just been
интересно ну просто с детства
interested in both jurisprudence since childhood. Well,
интересовала обеих юриспруденции Да ну
why is it that there are other
почему именно на прокурора есть другие
lawyers there for the prosecutor, for example,
там адвоката например
well, we study at the institute of the prosecutor’s office, but we’ll
ну Мы учимся в институте прокуратуры но
graduate, we can be anyone except a
мы выпустим можем быть кем угодно кроме
judge. We’ll also study. Well, do you want a lawyer to become a
судьи Мы ещё поду Ну хотите адвоката на
lawyer, as if they don’t teach them in
адвоката как бы не учат учат на
law in order to  to become a
юриспруденции для того чтобы стать
lawyer, you need to get a license, yes, yes,
адвокатом нужно получить ещё лицензию да
get an internship. You need to live with a
да получать практику Нужно там пожива у
lawyer there to be an assistant to a lawyer,
адвоката на быть помощником адвоката да
yes, yes, but you want to be a prosecutor, they
ну да но вы хотите быть прокурором
said, not a lawyer. Well, I would
сказали а не адвокатом Ну мне бы
like those from those, I want to join the investigative
хотелось те от те мне в следственный
committee, why, well, what’s wrong with that?
комитет хочется а почему вот ну что там
that it is prestigious to go there,
такого что именно туда престижно
good salary, lack of personnel in some
неплохая зарплата недостаток в некоторых
places So you
местах кадров Так что у тебя всегда
will always have
будет
a job But look, I just, well, I don’t
работа А вот смотрите Я просто Ну я не
know. There, I saw that you have an
знаю Там я видел что у вас там
investigative committee there, well, they are engaged in
следственный комитет э ну занимается и
all sorts of repressions. Yes, that’s where
репрессий всеми всякими Да вот там вот
they let you down  Just imagine, you
если вам спустят вот Представьте вы
work in the investigative committee, they let you
работаете в следственном комитете вам
down. For example, you need to
спустили Например нужно
fabricate some kind of Navalny. Yes, and what
сфабриковано Навального какого-то Да и
will you do? The prosecutor’s office is
что вы будете делать этим прокуратура
not involved in the investigative committee. Yeah.
занимается не следственный комитет Ага
Well, you’ll be in the prosecutor’s office And they’ll let you
Ну вот вы будете в прокуратуре И вам
down. What will you do to get something
спустят такое Что вы будете делать чтобы
like this down? It’s necessary even before this
такое спустили Нужно ещё до такого
to rise to the rank And that is, you are
дослужиться А то есть вы
like ordinary people, just ordinary
Типа люди обычные просто обычные
Prosecutors don’t do that
Прокуроры таким не занима
and what do they
а чем они
do is supervise the public
занимаются надзор за общественным
order of
порядком прав
human rights. So they send you to write
человека Вот вот вас отправляют написать
that everything is fine, all human rights are respected,
что всё нормально соблюдены все права
like yes,
человека типа
well. Usually, on the contrary,
да ну Обычно наоборот
the prosecutor’s office tries to identify everything
прокуратура старается выявлять всё
bad, that is,
плохое то есть
Uh-huh  look, you look like girls, I
Угу А вот смотрите вот вы как девушки
just also have a higher
вот у меня просто тоже есть высшее
education in law. I understand a little,
образование юридическое Я немножко
look. What do you think,
понимаю вот смотрите Как вы считаете
uh, Navalny
ээ Навального
was convicted legally, you mean, I want
осудили законно вы имеете в виду я хочу
you to tell them
вот чтобы вы их сказали
how you can’t say something like that.
как такое нельзя
That is, you really understand
высказывать То есть вы реально понимаете
that you live  in a system where you can’t
что вы живёте в системе где нельзя такое
say something like that Yes, because yes, but you go to
высказывать Да потому что да но идёте в
this system Well,
эту систему
where else to go for what kind of education
Ну а куда ещё идти под какое образование
besides legal prestige in Russia
кроме юридического престижа в России
in general we are not attracted to medicine
вообще медицина нас не привлекает
medicine to become a teacher bad salary
медицина стать учителем плохая зарплата
a huge number of personnel heavy
огромное количество кадров большая
workload philology Well, the majority
нагрузка филология Ну большинство
become teachers but also  not ours, that
становится учителями но тоже не наше то
is, we chose what we like Yes, there
есть мы выбрали то что нам по душе Да
are some problems in the
есть какие-то проблемы в
sim of
симе
others Well, in general, in the legal system in
других Ну вообще в юридической системе в
Russia Well, what can we do? Well, I’m right, it
России Ну а что поделать Ну я правильно
turns out that a talented person Yes,
получается что талантливому человеку Да
in Russia, in order to earn money you need to
в России чтобы заработать деньги нужно
go only to this  those who are rotten in the system
идти только вот в эту прогнившие систему
didn’t say that We need to go Where Where
так не сказали Мы нужно ити Куда Куда
you like where you want what your soul
нравится туда куда ты хочешь к чему душа
lies in, well, wait, your soul lies in a
лежит ну так подожди у вас лежит душа к
rotten system in which you are afraid to
прогнивший системы в которой вы боитесь
say legally or illegally to his servant We are
сказать законно или незаконно его слу мы
in the first year only teaching We are still
на первом курсе только учим мы пока ещё
learning  it’s been 100 years already Well, that is, you’re
до учимся уже 100 лет всё Ну то есть вам
already scared, you understand that you can’t
уже страшно вы вы понимаете что нельзя
talk and you’re going there to enroll, we’re not
говорить и идёте туда поступать нам не
scared, everything’s scary, we’ve
страшно всё страшно
switched, that’s for sure Like it,
переключились це точно Поставьте лайк
write Yes, fill out the comment, that’s definitely
пишиться Да залиште коментар це точно
published, we’ll edify the video, that’s even more
опубликовано буде окремим видео це дуже
showy in Russian, now I’ll say it’s
показового русски сейчас скажу это
just very-  very
просто очень-очень
cool They understand how rotten
круто Они понимают насколько прогнившая
this system is, they are afraid to say
Эта система они боятся сказать посадили
Navalny was imprisoned there, is it legal or illegal,
Навального там э законна или незаконна
and at the same time they go there Why
да и они при этом идут туда Почему
Because it’s possible to make money there and
Потому что там возможно сорвать бабло и
it’s prestigious, yes That’s the whole Russia
это престижно да Вот вот и вся Россия
system, you need to somehow get out among the people  there
система ты чтобы как-то выбиться в люди
must be this security officer
должен быть Вот этим силовиком
for the prosecutors And so on, who will
прокурорам И так дальше который будет
serve the system Yes, crush the people,
обслуживать систему Да давить народ
crush any
давить любые
signs of democracy Yes, all
паростки демократии Да всё
of this this video can’t show anything in full,
это этот ролик полноценно уже ничего не
I have no words Write Maybe you
всё у меня нет слов Напишите Может у вас
have in the comments write your
есть в комментариях напишите свои
words
слова
nay Telegram right now axis  VN
най Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube occupying
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and even
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
more richly video I don’t show people immediately don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we need to write an operational link in Mali
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and while there in the
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okm video more tezh tsikava  and
телеграме окм видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are responsible for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operative link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши